About Me

I am Stefanos Michael, a person really passionate with technology and science. I get involved into technology events and I've co-founded Brainstorm, I am a Microsoft Student Partner and a student member to various tech-related organizations, such as IEEE and StudentGuru Patras. The last two years I've started to get interested in Robotics, so I started my Thesis on Collaborative Localization Using V-INS in Evader-Pursuer Maneuvers.

Languages I speak





English - IGCSE (Grade B)

Work Experience

Brainstorm July 2011 - present

Founder and Developer

Brainstorm is a company focused on making quality mobile apps and games. Currently publishing for the Windows and Windows Phone platform, Brainstorm has a variety of hit-apps like the puzzle game Illuminate and the minimalistic text editor Write.

Microsoft Student Partner September 2012 - present

Student Partner

The main responsibilities of being a Microsoft Student Partner are to organize events, seminars and trainings at the University, to promote the company's tools and technologies and to be the contact point between professors, students and the company.

National Guard July 2008 - July 2010

Infantry Sergeant

I've served my country as an Infantry Sergeant with an Anti-Tank Specialty and I've also been an office assistant in "Millitary Education & Information Office".



STEFANOS MICHAEL **Electrical & Computer Engineer**

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+







Skills

Get in touch:

stefanos990.com

facebok.com/stefanos990 twitter.com/stefanos990

linkedin.com/in/stefanos990

Education

University of Patras September 2010 - July 2015 (expected)

Department - Electrical & Computer Engineering

Thesis - Collaborative Localization Using V-INS in Evader-Pursuer Maneuvers

Current GPA - 7.18 / 10.00 **Expected GPA** - 7.50 / 10.00

Paralimni Lyceum (High School) September 2005 - June 2008

GPA - 19.75 / 20.00

Organizations

IEEE January 2011 - present

Student Member

IEEE is the world's largest professional association dedicated to advancing technological innovation and excellence for the benefit of humanity. IEEE and its members inspire a global community through IEEE's highly cited publications, conferences, technology standards, and professional and educational activities.

StudentGuru Patras September 2012 - present

Member

StudentGuru is one of the biggest student forums in Greece with more than 14.000 members, focusing on technology. Its offline events are organised by local communities. StudentGuru Patras is the first academic community in University of Patras majoring in Microsoft .NET related technologies. It was founded in October 2009 and its main vision is to bring students closer to popular technologies.

Skills and Personal Attributes





STEFANOS MICHAEL
Electrical & Computer Engineer

Paralimni, Cyprus

17/05/1990

DATE OF BIRTH

15+
PROJECTS
DELIVERED

About Me

Work Experience

Education

Skills

Get in touch:

■ stefanos990@outlook.com

stefanos990.com

facebok.com/stefanos990 twitter.com/stefanos990

in linkedin.com/in/stefanos990